http://www.lifeloc.com/privacy

Vietnamese
Welcome to Lifeloc!
Log In
Search:
Search
0
You have no items in your shopping cart.
0
Study Shows No Detectable Chance of Catching Virus from Cross Contamination Using Lifeloc Breath Alcohol Testers
Sentinel Alcohol System
R.A.D.A.R. Alcohol Detection and Reporting System Calibration Equipment
Sentinel Alcohol System
R.A.D.A.R. Alcohol Detection and Reporting System Calibration Equipment
Industry Solutions
Law EnforcementWorkplaceCorrectionsSchoolsOil & GasMilitary Chiropractic
Industry Solutions
Law EnforcementWorkplaceCorrectionsSchoolsOil & GasMilitary Chiropractic
International Solutions
Alcohol Testing
Professional
Sentinel Alcohol SystemAlcoMark Breath Testing Management Software
Professional
Sentinel Alcohol SystemAlcoMark Breath Testing Management Software
Provisional Instructor Training
FC Series TrainingCertification ExplainedTraining FAQsRequest Training Info
Provisional Instructor Training
FC Series TrainingCertification ExplainedTraining FAQsRequest Training Info
Service
Extended Service Plans Recerts & Diagnostics Rentals Calibration WarrantyPhoenix 6.0 FAQFC20 FAQFC10/FC10Plus FAQ
Service
Extended Service Plans Recerts & Diagnostics Rentals Calibration WarrantyPhoenix 6.0 FAQFC20 FAQFC10/FC10Plus FAQ
BAC Measurement
R.A.D.A.R.® is the most advanced breath alcohol monitoring system, combining cutting-edge biometric technology with a humane, minimally disruptive approach to transform lives.
R.A.D.A.R.® is the most advanced breath alcohol monitoring system, combining cutting-edge biometric technology with a humane, minimally disruptive approach to transform lives.
R.A.D.A.R.® is the most advanced breath alcohol monitoring system, combining cutting-edge biometric technology with a humane, minimally disruptive approach to transform lives.
R.A.D.A.R.® is the most advanced breath alcohol monitoring system, combining cutting-edge biometric technology with a humane, minimally disruptive approach to transform lives.
R.A.D.A.R.® is the most advanced breath alcohol monitoring system, combining cutting-edge biometric technology with a humane, minimally disruptive approach to transform lives.
Home
>
Lifeloc Technologies Internet Privacy and Security Policy
×
Login Form
E-mail address *
Password *
Forgot Password ?
Login
or registration
×
Registration
Profile Informations
First Name *
Last Name *
Subscribe to Newsletter
or login
First name is required!
Last name is required!
First name is not valid!
Last name is not valid!
This is not an email address!
Email address is required!
This email is already registered!
Password is required!
Enter a valid password!
Please enter 6 or more characters!
Please enter 16 or less characters!
Passwords are not same!
Terms and Conditions are required!
Email or Password is wrong!
Privacy Policy
Our Commitment to Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
Scope of Policy
This Policy applies to www.lifeloc.com site, operated by Lifeloc Technologies, Inc. It does not apply to other companies' or organizations' web sites to which we link. It does not apply to any other websites or web properties operated by Lifeloc Technologies, Inc. Carefully review the privacy policies of those web sites in order to determine how they treat your personal information.
Personal Information
We do not collect personal information about our website users except when knowingly provided by such individuals. We may require that you provide personal information in order to register, purchase and/or participate in certain services we offer. We may use your information to provide you with products or services that you have requested or to provide you with promotional offers that we believe will be of interest to you.
We respect your privacy and under no circumstances do we sell, rent, trade or share your information with those outside Lifeloc Technologies, Inc.
This policy is effective from January 1, 2011
What We May Collect
We may collect the following information:
name and job title
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postal code, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer warranty registration and various products and services we provide
temporary Debit/Credit Card information to complete a transaction. We do not store Debit/Credit Card information permanently.
Our Commitment to Children's Privacy
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information from those we know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.
What We Do with the Information We Gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with better service, and in particular, for the following reasons:
To complete a sales or other business transaction with you.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional email about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.
Security
We have implemented procedures to help protect the personal information that you provide to us. However, no method of transmitting or storing of electronic data is ever completely secure, and we cannot guarantee that such information will never be accessed, used, or released in a manner that is inconsistent with this policy.
How We Use Cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. The file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets site operators know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
When you visit www.lifeloc.com, we may assign your computer a cookie to remember who you are. We also may include other information in our cookie files; for example, if you arrived via a link from third-party site, we may include the URL of the linking page. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to Other Websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website.
Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement.
Terms & Conditions
Please visit our Terms and Conditions of Use page establishing the use, disclaimers and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.
Your Consent
By using www.lifeloc.com you consent to the Privacy Policy as stated herein.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions concerning our Privacy Policy you may contact us at corporateinfo@lifeloc.com
Location & Hours
12441 W. 49th Ave, Suite 4Wheat Ridge, CO 80033Phone: 303.431.9500M-F 7:30am - 5pm MSTContact Us
© 2017 Lifeloc Technologies Inc. All Rights Reserved.
